A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants Them-Tw FA732H FA732H
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - Them to Tw, 1937-2006
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07500639), 1975 September 01-1977 August 31 (Reel R1249)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR LEGAL SERVICE ACTIVITIES ON BEHALF OF POOR PERSONS AND LOCAL LAW PROGRAMS REPRESENTING INDIGENT
    $62,500.00;$19,967.08
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07550307), 1975 March 15-1977 December 31 (Reel R1433)
    FOR A STUDY OF POSSIBLE RELATIONS BETWEEN NUTRITION AND NEUROLOGICAL HANDICAPS IN CHILDREN.
    $20,644.00;$20,644.00
    Chafkin, Sol H.;Cooney, Thomas E.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07600111), 1976 January 01-1977 December 31 (Reel R1348, Reel R4052)
    TO EVALUATE THE INTERRATIONSHIP BETWEEN CALIFORNIA AND FEDERAL PLANNING REGULATION AND DEVELOPMENT OF LOW/MODERATE INCOME HOUSING
    $25,000.00;$14,520.45
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07600258), 1976 April 01-1979 December 31 (Reel R2507)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR EXPANSION OF THE SUMMER PROGRAM FOR MINORITY JOURNALISTS AT SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM
    National Affairs [NA];Office of Communications (pre 1979)
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07600287), 1976 January 01-1980 October 01 (Reel R2741)
    RESEARCH ON HIGHER EDUCATION FINANCE AND ADMINISTRATION
    $148,710.58;$148,710.58
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07600438), 1976 July 01-1978 January 31 (Reel R1226)
    COMPARATIVE STUDY OF BUDGETING AND RESOURCE ALLOCATION FOR HIGHER EDUCATION IN SELECTED EUROPEAN COUNTRIES
    $45,950.00;$43,899.44
    Bischoff, Irma E.;Crossland, Fred E. (Fred Eugene);Ruof, Peter
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07600608), 1976 September 30-1977 September 29 (Reel R2431)
    DEVELOPMENT OF A POLICY MODEL FOR THE ACADEMIC LABOR MARKET
    $72,562.00;$.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07600620), 1976 October 01-1978 March 31 (Reel R2306)
    SUPPORT FOR A CASE STUDY OF THE FUNCTIONING OF THE ACADEMIC LABOR MARKET CONDUCTED BY PROFESSOR NEIL J. SMELSER
    $31,357.00;$31,357.00
    Bischoff, Irma E.;Chamberlain, Mariam
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07650052), 1975 October 15-1977 April 15 (Reel R1339)
    SUPPORT FOR THE PRINTING AND DISSEMINATION OF A REPORT ON "MATHEMATICS AND SEX"
    $13,134.00;$13,107.76
    Chamberlain, Mariam;Saario, Terry
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07650139), 1976 January 01-1976 September 30 (Reel R1500)
    PROPOSAL FOR DESIGN OF MULTIFAMILY INTERVENTION DEMONSTRATION PROJECT IN CONJUNCTION WITH HUD REGION IX
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07650592), 1976 September 30-1977 September 28 (Reel R1192)
    SUPPORT TO THE INSTITUTE'S SOVIET-AMERICAN CONFERENCE ON ASIA
    $5,876.00;$5,876.00
    Bresnan, John J.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07700037), 1976 November 01-1978 June 30 (Reel R2993, Reel R2994)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF MAJOR INFLUENCES ON AMERICAN POLITICS AND POLICIES
    $152,243.00;$152,243.00
    Lisniewski, Theresa H.;Saario, Terry
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07700202), 1977 February 15-1977 April 14 (Reel R1240)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A DEMONSTRATION EFFORT TO IMPROVE THE OPERATIONOF DISTRESSED HUD MULTIFAMILY HOUSING DEVELOPMENTS IN CALIFORNIA
    $175,000.00;$.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07750215), 1977 January 15-1978 June 30 (Reel R2966)
    DEVELOPMENT OF THE MINORITY LABOR LEADERSHIP TRAINING PROGRAM AND ITS INSTITUTIONALIZATION INTO THE CALIF. COMMUNITY COLLEGE SYSTEM
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07750453), 1977 May 01-1978 July 31 (Reel R4641)
    PUBLICATION AND DISTRIBUTION OF "COMMENT" ISSUE ON THE SYMPOSIUM, "CONTRACEPTIVE HORMONES AND HUMAN WELFARE."
    $10,032.00;$10,032.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07850384), 1978 March 01-1980 April 30 (Reel R2920)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A PROJECT TO EXPLORE MAJOR ISSUES OF U.S. FOOD POLICY
    $14,300.00;$13,336.85
    Hertford, Reed;Lisniewski, Theresa H.;Sharpe, Richard S.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07850570), 1978 June 01-1979 November 30 (Reel R2504, Reel R4052, Reel R5203)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF THE INTEGRATION OF WOMEN INTO THE U.S. COAST GUARD ACADEMY
    $17,250.00;$17,250.00
    Chamberlain, Mariam;Lynch, Barbara D.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07850579), 1978 July 01-1978 December 31 (Reel R1363, Reel R1364)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF SYMPOSIUM AT RACINE, WISCONSIN TO DISCUSS IMPLICATIONS OF FORTHCOMING SUPREME COURT "BAKKE" DECISION
    $12,290.00;$12,290.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07850623), 1978 September 01-1979 May 31 (Reel R1367)
    DEVELOPMENT OF PROJECT ENTITLED "MORAL MEANING AND SOCIAL COMMITMENT IN AMERICA"
    $5,060.00;$5,060.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07900084), 1979 January 25-1981 June 30 (Reel R2681)
    RESEARCH ON THE EFFECTS OF PROPOSITION 13 ON HIRING, WAGES, AND COLLECTIVE BARGAINING IN CALIFORNIA LOCAL GOVERNMENTS
    $70,011.00;$70,011.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07900333), 1979 March 01-1982 March 31 (Reel R3044)
    SUPPORT OF RESEARCH ON "THE SECOND ECONOMY OF THE SOVIET UNION"
    $73,150.00;$73,150.00
    Gaer, Felice D.
    Soviet Union
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07950052), 1978 September 16-1979 September 15 (Reel R4219)
    SUPPORT FOR AMERICAN SEAMEN EXCHANGE PROGRAM
    $12,635.00;$12,635.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07950126), 1979 January 01-1980 December 31 (Reel R2306)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND WRITING ON THE TOPIC OF SCHOOLS AND GOVERNMENT
    $19,422.00;$19,365.79
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07950325), 1979 May 01-1981 April 30 (Reel R3758, Reel R4329, Reel R5049)
    STUDIES IN CONTEMPORARY SUDANESE HISTORY
    $23,100.00;$22,857.09
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07950610), 1979 July 01-1980 September 30 (Reel R2212)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF RESEARCH AND PUBLICATION ON MORAL PROBLEMS IN UNIVERSITY CONTEXT
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (07950732), 1979 September 01-1984 March 31 (Reel R4642)
    SUPPORT OF RESEARCH PROJECT ON "THE MORAL BASIS OF SOCIAL COMMITMENT IN AMERICA"
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08000459), 1980 April 14-1983 December 31 (Reel R4595)
    SUPPORT TO ESTABLISH A RESEARCH PROGRAM ON WOMEN AND THEIR WORK
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08000703), 1980 June 01-1981 February 28 (Reel R3569)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON "INTERGENERATIONAL TRANSFER OF DEPENDENCE"
    $21,600.00;$21,505.63
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08050305), 1979 November 01-1980 May 31 (Reel R4413)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A CONFERENCE OF SOVIET AND AMERICAN SCHOLARS ONASIAN RELATIONS
    North Asia
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08050557), 1980 May 15-1980 August 14 (Reel R2700, Reel R3823)
    SUPPORT LECTURES BY THAI WRITER KHAMSING SRINAWK AT UNIVERSITY'S CENTER FOR SOUTH AND SOUTHEAST ASIAN STUDIES
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08050752), 1980 September 01-1981 August 31 (Reel R3069)
    SUPPORT OF RESEARCH ON "THE ROLE OF JAPAN IN SOUTH KOREAN SECURITY"
    $17,100.00;$17,100.00
    Japan; Korea (South)
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08100310), 1981 March 01-1982 April 30 (Reel R3703)
    SUPPORT FOR A COMPARATIVE ANALYSIS OF CHANGES IN RURAL COMMUNITIES
    $83,000.00;$83,000.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08100911), 1981 October 01-1983 March 31 (Reel R4320)
    PROJECT TO INCREASE HISPANIC ENROLLMENT IN MATH-BASED FIELDS OF STUDY
    $45,700.00;$45,639.88
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08150415), 1981 March 01-1981 August 31 (Reel R4053)
    SUPPORT FOR CONFERENCE AND WORKSHOP ON ISSUES AND PROBLEMS OF MINORITIES IN MATHEMATICS
    $24,848.00;$24,741.95
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08150448), 1981 May 01-1981 October 31 (Reel R3654)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF TENTH SINO-AMERICAN CONFERENCE ON CHINA
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08150486), 1981 July 01-1982 December 31 (Reel R3739)
    SUPPORT OF A STUDY OF THE FINANCING OF VOCATIONAL EDUCATION
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08150591), 1981 April 01-1982 March 31 (Reel R4356)
    EXPLORATION OF THE RELATIONSHIP OF U.S. AGRICULTURAL COMMODITY SYSTEMS AND PUBLIC POLICY
    $13,123.00;$12,803.47
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08150593), 1981 July 01-1982 September 30 (Reel R3631, Reel R3632)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF CHILDHOOD AND PUBLIC POLICY
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08151048), 1981 October 01-1983 May 31 (Reel R4250)
    SUPPORT OF RESEARCH ON RURAL INDUSTRIALIZATION
    $11,000.00;$11,000.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08200955), 1982 March 01-1984 June 30 (Reel R4320)
    TO SUPPORT THE UNIVERSITY'S RURAL DEVELOPMENT POLICY PROJECT
    $171,226.00;$171,226.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08250605), 1982 March 01-1982 June 30 (Reel R3043)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON INTERNATIONAL SECURITY AND ARMS CONTROL
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08250625), 1982 June 01-1985 September 30 (Reel R4691)
    TO CONTINUE RESEARCH ON "THE SECOND ECONOMY OF THE SOVIET UNION"
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08250646), 1982 March 01-1982 May 31 (Reel R4251, Reel R5316)
    SUPPORT FOR A SEMINAR ON EXCHANGE PROGRAM WITH PLANNERS IN THE FEDERAL DISTRICT
    Cleaves, Peter S.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08250756), 1982 September 01-1984 June 30 (Reel R4229, Reel R4230)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF POLITICAL ORIENTATIONS OF PROVINCIAL PARTY SECRETARIES IN THE U.S.S.R.
    $27,809.00;$27,809.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08250824), 1982 July 01-1984 June 30 (Reel R4225)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A QUADRILATERAL RESEARCH PROJECT ON "DEVELOPMENT, STABILITY AND SECURITY IN THE PACIFIC-ASIAN REGION"
    North Asia; SouthEast Asia
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08350088), 1982 September 01-1983 August 31 (Reel R4521)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON "IMPACTS OF LIMITED WATER FOR AGRICULTURE IN THE ARID WEST"
    $10,000.00;$.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08350728), 1983 August 01-1984 December 31 (Reel R4682)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A SERIES OF SYMPOSIA ENTITLED "PEACE AND WAR: ANTHROPOLOGICAL PERSPECTIVES"
    $28,469.00;$28,050.49
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08350743), 1982 November 01-1985 September 30 (Reel R5269)
    RESEARCH AND WRITING OF BOOK ON SOUTH AFRICAN LIBERATION MOVEMENTS
    $32,935.00;$32,935.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08400503), 1984 July 01-1985 September 30 (Reel R4985)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT TO MODIFY AND EXTEND ITS BAY AREA MATHEMATICS PROJECT
    $64,100.00;$63,482.34
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08400718), 1984 September 01-1988 April 30 (Reel R5612)
    SUPPORT FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF AN ADVANCED DEGREE CONSORTIUM AMONG COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES SERVING NATIVE AMERICAN STUDENTS
    $240,800.00;$240,800.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08450515), 1984 June 15-1985 June 14 (Reel R4533)
    SUPPORT FOR A WORKSHOP ON THE FOREIGN ECONOMIC STRATEGIES OF EAST EUROPEAN COUNTRIES
    $4,112.00;$1,749.15
    Bayard, Thomas O.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08450944), 1984 September 01-1986 December 31 (Reel R5291)
    STUDY ON INTERNATIONAL ECONOMY OF GOVERNMENT DECISION-MAKING PROCEDURES FOR TRADE & INVESTMENT POLICY FOR HIGH TECH/U.S.& JAPAN
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08450950), 1984 October 01-1986 October 31 (Reel R5643)
    SUPPORT FOR A BOOK ANALYZING U.S. SOCIAL WELFARE POLICIES IN AN INTERNATIONAL COMPARATIVE CONTEXT (WELFARE STATE)
    Arnold, David D.;Hamilton, Charles V.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08500421), 1985 May 14-1994 July 09 (Reel R6749, Reel R7285)
    SUPPORT FOR SOCIAL FORESTRY POLICY RESEARCH IN SOUTH ASIA
    $376,250.00;$376,250.00
    Campbell, J. Y. (Jeffrey Y.);Khan, Asmeen Mariam;Capistrano, Ana Doris
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08500906), 1985 September 01-1989 February 28 (Reel R5786)
    ESTABLISH HISTORY EDUCATION CTR. AT SCHOOL OF EDUC.& FUND 3 YRS OF INSERVICE WORKSHO.FOR TEACHERS OF REQ. US & WORLD HISTORY COURSES
    $275,083.00;$275,083.00
    Stanley, Peter W.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08550187), 1984 December 15-1985 December 14 (Reel R4587)
    SUBSIDY TO THE UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA PRESS FOR PUBLICATION OF "ETHNIC GROUPS IN CONFLICT"
    Geithner, Peter F.;Morris, Diana L.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08550499), 1985 April 01-1986 July 01 (Reel R5232, Reel R5235)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF PUENTE PROJECT: WRITING AND COUNSELING PROGRAM FOR MEXICAN AMERICAN STUDENTS
    $49,978.00;$49,978.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08600904), 1986 July 01-1987 September 30 (Reel R5291)
    PLANNING A STUDY ON TESTING ISSUES AS THEY PERTAIN TO MINORITIES IN THE AREAS OF EMPLOYMENT AND EDUCATION
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08650018), 1985 November 01-1987 August 31 (Reel R5348)
    CORE SUPPORT FOR A U.S.-CHINA AFRICAN STUDIES EXCHANGE PROGRAM
    $54,070.00;$54,070.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08650605), 1986 July 01-1987 December 31 (Reel R4790)
    SUPPORT FOR PROJECT ON "THE ECONOMICS OF CONFLICT AND SETTLEMENT"
    $49,904.00;$49,904.00
    Bayard, Thomas O.;Schoettle, Enid C. B.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08700743), 1987 June 01-1991 June 30 (Reel R6190)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON THE FACTORS THAT HAVE PROMOTED OR IMPEDED DIFFERENT COUNTRIES' ADJUSTMENTS TO INTERNATIONAL DISTURBANCES
    $122,245.00;$120,352.30
    O'Cleireacain, Seamus
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08700770), 1987 June 01-1990 May 31 (Reel R6183, Reel R6184)
    SUPPORT OF A COMMISSION ON TESTING ISSUES, ESPECIALLY AS THEY PERTAIN TO MINORITIES IN THE AREAS OF EMPLOYMENT AND EDUCATION
    Stanley, Peter W.;Huntley, Lynn
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08750222), 1987 February 01-1989 April 30 (Reel R5987)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON PARALLELS AND DISSIMILARITIES IN ASIAN COMMUNIST SOCIETIES
    $44,000.00;$40,446.82
    Korea (North)
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08750366), 1987 March 01-1988 December 31 (Reel R6402)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A RESEARCH PROJECT ON THE HISTORY OF "ENGLISH ONLY" MOVEMENTS IN THE U.S.
    $50,000.00;$48,360.33
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08750432), 1987 May 01-1988 April 30 (Reel R5555)
    SUPPORT A MID-CAREER FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM FOR BLACK SOUTH AFRICANS
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08750487), 1987 May 01-1987 December 31 (Reel R5575)
    SUPPORT FOR A MEETING ON THE NEEDS OF SCHOLARS IN THE FIELD OF SOVIET/EAST EUROPEAN AGRICULTURAL ECONOMICS
    $5,000.00;$3,026.09
    Trebat, Thomas J.
    Soviet Union; Europe, Eastern
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08751142), 1987 October 01-1989 June 30 (Reel R5944)
    SUPPORT FOR A RESEARCH AGENDA ON U.S. COMPETITIVENESS AND COOPERATION FOR THE NATION'S BUSINESS SCHOOLS
    Tosterud, Robert;Trebat, Thomas J.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08800876), 1988 July 01-1991 August 31 (Reel R6212)
    MATCHING SUPPORT FOR A PROJECT TO IMPROVE TEACHING AT SELECTED TWO- AND FOUR-YEAR COLLEGES
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08801133), 1988 October 14-2001 December 31 (Reel R8881)
    $80,000.00;$53,214.60
    Salole, Gerry
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08850096), 1987 November 06-1992 December 31 (Reel R6512)
    SUPPORT FOR THE U.S.-INDIA BILATERAL FORUM TO BE HELD IN NEW DELHI
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08850183), 1988 January 01-1989 December 31 (Reel R5707)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON "IRAN, THE UNITED STATES, AND THE USSR"
    $29,180.00;$28,923.63
    Iran; Soviet Union; United States
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08850201), 1987 October 01-1988 January 31 (Reel R5497, Reel R6071)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON TRADITIONAL WET FIELD AGRICULTURE IN THE AMERICAN AND ASIAN TROPICS
    $4,400.00;$4,400.00
    Chand, Marian McClure
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08900205), 1989 January 01-1989 December 31 (Reel R6035)
    SUMMER INSTITUTES FOR MINORITY UNDERGRADUATES TO PREPARE FOR GRADUATE PUBLIC POLICY & INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS STUDIES
    Diaz, William A.;Heginbotham, Stanley J. (Stanely Jay)
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08950175), 1988 July 01-1990 December 31 (Reel R6416)
    FOR SUPPORT OF A STUDY OF THE MASS MEDIA AND THE HISPANIC ELECTORATE IN THE 1988 PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
    $37,000.00;$37,000.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08950541), 1989 April 01-1989 October 01 (Reel R5803, Reel R5969)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON UNITED STATES-CHINA RELATIONS IN THE 1990S
    $17,250.00;$15,495.96
    Geithner, Peter F.;Harkness, James S.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (08950941), 1989 August 01-1990 July 31 (Reel R5705)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE INAUGURATING A SOVIET-U.S. ACADEMIC DIALOGUE ON HUMAN RIGHTS
    Soviet Union; United States; Global
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09001143), 1990 July 01-1996 June 30 (Reel R7331)
    CONTINUED SUPPORT FOR TWO PUBLICLY SUPPORTED AND NONPROFIT SOCIAL SERVICE PROJECTS
    $585,000.00;$585,000.00
    Mincy, Ronald B.;Kubisch, Anne C.
    California; Social service--United States; Public welfare--United States
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09001482), 1990 October 01-1995 June 30 (Reel R7020)
    SUPPORT FOR J.D. & GRADUATE FELLOWSHIPS & STUDENT RESEARCH ASSISTANTSHIPS AT THE BERKELEY SCHOOL OF LAW (011)
    $480,000.00;$480,000.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09050605), 1990 April 01-1992 June 30 (Reel R6254)
    SUPPORT FOR INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON CALIFORNIA HIGHER EDUCATION POLICY TO BE HELD AT THE CENTER FOR STUDIES IN HIGHER EDUCATION
    $12,000.00;$12,000.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09051183), 1990 July 01-1991 June 30 (Reel R6621)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE MINORITY EDUCATION PROJECT
    Urban Poverty Program [UP];Education & Culture Program [EC]
    Brown, Prudence;Hatton, Barbara R.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09051315), 1990 September 01-1995 January 31 (Reel R6581)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE SECOND INTERNATIONAL CONGRESS OF ETHNOBIOLOGY
    Coward, E. Walter
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09051420), 1990 September 01-1991 June 01 (Reel R5799, Reel R6154)
    SUPPORT FOR SOUTHEAST ASIANS TO PARTICIPATE IN THE SECOND INTERNATIONAL CONGRESS OF ETHNOBIOLOGY
    $11,119.00;$11,119.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09101288), 1991 September 01-1995 August 31 (Reel R7276)
    TO PROVIDE SUPPORT FOR THE DEPARTMENT OF AFRO-AMERICAN STUDIES TO STRENGTHEN ITS UNDERGRADUATE PROGRAM AND INTERDISCIPLINARY RESEARCH ON THE AFRICAN DIASPORA
    Petrovich, Janice
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09101380), 1991 September 01-1991 December 31 (Reel R6497)
    SUPPORT TO DEVELOP TRAINING AND TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE CAPACITY TO DELIVER COMPREHENSIVE SERVICES TO POOR FAMILIES
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09150404), 1991 January 01-1992 December 31 (Reel R6570)
    SUPPORT FOR A BILATERAL INDIA-U.S. CONFERENCE ON POLITICAL, ECONOMIC, AND SECURITY ISSUES TO BE HELD IN BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA
    $31,990.00;$30,972.37
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09200103), 1991 October 01-2004 September 30 (Reel R9071)
    Support for a project on "Economic and Institutional Factors in Global Economic Growth" (023)
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09200178), 1991 September 01-1993 September 30 (Reel R7072, Reel R7247)
    SUPPORT TO STRENGTHEN LEGAL EDUCATION AND RESEARCH IN CHINA
    $625,354.00;$625,354.00
    Chang, Phyllis L.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09200791), 1992 June 01-1998 May 31 (Reel R8167)
    PREPARATION OF A UNIVERSITY TEXTBOOK ON RURAL DEVELOPMENT ECONOMICS
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09201155), 1992 July 01-1995 June 30 (Reel R6824)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF THE MEANING OF LOW-WAGE SERVICE JOBS IN THE LIVES OF MINORITY ADOLESCENTS
    Brown, Prudence;Fulbright-Anderson, Karen
    Oakland (Calif.)
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09251275), 1992 March 01-1993 February 28 (Reel R6380)
    PROJECT SUPPORT TO PUBLISH "LA RAZA LAW JOURNAL" SYMPOSIUM PROCEEDINGS ON VOTING RIGHTS AND REDISTRICTING
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09301182), 1993 July 01-1999 June 30 (Reel R8925)
    SUPPORT FOR INTERDISCIPLINARY WORKSHOP/SEMINARS THAT BRING TOGETHER FACULTY AND STUDENTS FROM THE SOCIAL SCIENCES AND AREA STUDIES
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09350271), 1993 January 01-1993 July 01 (Reel R6628)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON "SOUTH ASIA: BALANCING ECONOMIC REFORM WITH POLITICAL SECURITY"
    International Affairs Program [IA];Asia & The Pacific [ASIA]
    $13,000.00;$12,659.78
    Geithner, Peter F.;O'Cleireacain, Seamus
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09350676), 1993 April 01-1995 March 31 (Reel R6905)
    RESEARCH ON EFFECTIVENESS AND IMPACT OF REGISTRATION PROCEDURES ASSOCIATED WITH IMPLEMENTATION OF "MOTOR VOTER" LEGISLATION
    $41,000.00;$41,000.00
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09401262), 1994 July 01-2000 March 31 (Reel R8677)
    SUPPORT FOR A BINATIONAL STUDY OF DEMOCRACY AND PLURALISM IN INDIA AND THE UNITED STATES
    Asia & The Pacific [ASIA];India, Nepal and Sri Lanka (New Delhi)
    Robinson, Mark
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09450722), 1994 May 01-1994 October 31 (Reel R6744)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON WOMEN IN TRANSITION IN LAOS, VIETNAM AND CHINA TO BE HELD IN BANGKOK, JUNE 1994
    China; Laos; Vietnam
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09501164), 1995 September 01-2000 August 31 (Reel R8450)
    SUPPORT FOR A PROGRAM OF GRADUATE TRAINING AND RESEARCH ON THE CAUCASUS
    Education & Culture Program [EC];International Affairs Program [IA]
    Biddle, Sheila;Grudzinska-Gross, Irena;Stewart-Hill, Anne;Volkman, Toby Alice
    Armenia; Azerbaijan; Georgia (Republic)
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09501523), 1995 September 01-1999 October 31 (Reel R8542)
    SUPPORT FOR THE DEPARTMENT OF AFRICAN STUDIES FOR PROJECT ON "AFRICAN DIASPORA STUDIES, MULTICULTURALISM, AND IDENTITY CONSTRUCTION"
  - The Regents of the University of California, Berkeley (09501524), 1995 September 01-2000 September 30 (Reel R8565)